obsolescence
dying
i fear always living in poverty
i fear falling out of a jet plane at 30000 feet because it is crashing into the ocean or the ground. It's been my fear since I was a little girl
my greatest fear is that my kids might have to experience pain and suffering
to be without my family and friends
i am terrified of flying
i fear disappointing my mom
i have stage fright and find it difficult to talk and voice my opinion in a group setting where there are a large number of people
snakes
being alone
not being able to provide for family
watching all of my loved ones die. In a perfect world, my parents would live forever and I wouldn't even have to think about this 
seeing my wife lose her mother and grandmother less than a year apart broke my heart. She is so sad and depressed
my biggest fear is being buried alive. In this day and age, it seems almost impossible. However, it is a big fear of mine
1. Becoming an unkind or hot-tempered individual 2. Spiders 3. Being invisible and unheard
an earthquake
what I fear most is living long enough to suffer the way I've seen my older relatives suffer and be unable to make choices independently
my biggest fear is pain -- specifically, a grand mal seizure, because I have had one before
losing my husband
spiders. It's horrible. I have the WORST panic attacks
marriage
Something bad happening to my children
i think my greatest fear is losing my husband. He's my best friend and the thought of living without him is pure misery
rejection and spiders are my biggest fear in life
never falling in love
speaking to a crowd
my children being seriously hurt or dying
i guess I fear being alone most. I would hate to die alone
i fear thefts, which have became common nowadays. i fear most of the time when i go out
i  fear snakes
as I get older what I fear most is death. It is the fear of the unknown
living alone without my husband my whole life due to immigration issues
i most fear for God. God only knows everything about our life. So, I always fear only for God
only fear i have in my life is my husband. I hate him like anything
death
what I fear the most is a total economic collapse. This is a great concern as it would be a struggle to eat and find money
since the recession, I have not been able to get on my feet sense and am still having a difficult time surviving
i fear that my kids will not be able to survive in the world today
i fear alot of things like thunderstorms,lighting, crowds,social situactions,open  spaces, doctors,dentist, being disabled and not being able to pay my utlties
i fear heights. If I am on the top floor of 5 floor building, my legs will shiver if i look downwards
i'm not afraid of lizards or spiders if they stick to the wall but when they move, I feel some hot air go out from my ears
it is a great concern that my kids will not be able to take care of themselves
i fear darkness
losing my job so that I cannot support my family
being cheated on or scammed
being alone
although probably pretty cliche, I would say failure
i am in the process of making a lot of sacrifices in order to pursue a specific career, and I am terrified that in the end, it will end up being all for naught
growing old with not enough money and having to live in tough conditions
spiders
i am always in fear of death
that humanity will not find some common ground in order to solve our problems here on planet earth
many of us find life unbearable and are experiencing a sensation of emptiness and lack of purpose
that my decisions will get others hurt or killed
i fear being poor for the rest of my life and always being in debt and unable to pay for things I need like food, health care or even a burial plot and coffin when I die
i fear that things are never going to get better and it will just keep getting worse
things I fear: terrorists, violence, robbery, assault, spiders, snakes, wild animals
i fear dying the most of anything in life
my greatest fear is that I will fail in life
i fear the death of a family member
death
a crazy person with a weapon
health issues that may cause me to not be around to see my young son become a man
not graduating college and being stuck in a low paying dead end job
not being able to be independent 
not being able to provide for my family
getting sick and having no one to take care of me
when the person that I am, meets the person I could have become
i fear being shocked! Even static electricity. Also, bees. I flip out even if a fly is buzzing around
flying
my appendix bursting
i fear that if anything happens to me my kids will end up with my mom which is okay but my mom is getting older herself
death
failure. I always have tried to be the best, the smartest. I am afraid that one day I will not get there; that I will fall flat on my face
i have a ridiculously horrid fear of dreadlocks. I can't be near them. If they touch me I lose my mind
being unsuccessful
helplessness
to have a broken family
i fear dying
i fear dying while my kids are young because I don't have much help in my family
fear of Death
needles, semi trucks, and spiders
not falling in love
one of my biggest fears in life is spiders, I am severely afraid of even the smallest spider
financial insecurity, death of family members
dying, spiders, being lost without my gps
what I fear the most is to die alone. I want my family and friends around me when I take my last breath. I want to feel comforted in my time of need
being alone in life and death
i fear being locked in a room that has filled with poisonous snakes, sharks and alligators while slowly filling up with water and is pitch black
dying unexpectedly and leaving my four young children without a mother. My second fear is cats I am terrified of them
i fear snakes i do not like them they are scary and i would not want to be attacked by one
not having a home to live in and food on the table
death. I often fear about it and think why in this world, God has made this as inevitable
not having enough money to pay bills
every day I have more afraid of humans because they are capable of any atrocity
what I fear most in my life is the possibility of losing one of my children
i am a  homeless person. I am trying to buy a home. But I don't have enough money
dying alone
physical torture
what I fear most in my life is losing my children
talking to other people
i fear not being loved
large groups of people
i fear failure in life. Failure to not be able to make a living, but I don't admit it to anyone but you because I believe what you fear you attract
i'm afraid of being a penniless bum
i fear the return of severe depression
one of my immediate family members dying too soon
i fear not having security - a place to live, food to eat, money
failure to provide for my family
my family dying, particularly my father
the thing which i fear the most is reptiles
snakes and heights
mot being able to have children of my own is my biggest fear in life
drowning
to die
making choices that further cause damage or harm to my children. Choices that I have made in the past have changed how they see themselves, and their place in the world
running out of money
i fear for the scary movies
that one day I will run across something I am afraid of
i fear that nobody really loves me and anyone who says they are is lying or pretending
i fear losing my family member and committing suicide
i fear poverty the most. It is the most difficult thing to come out of. Thinking of not being able to make ends meet in day to day life is very scary
i fear that I won't make enough of a difference to create change
like most of us I fear many things but to me the worst is probably being old and alone
heights
i fear about the existence of ghosts
suffering
never being able to obtain a true sense of contentment in my life
i fear that i will forever be struggling in life, constantly just getting by. I want to be successful, so i fear being unsuccessful
i fear that one day I will wake and everything that I hold dearest to me will not be there and I will be lost and alone
i fear the day when I grow to tired to be ambitious
diseases 
losing all my memories
i fear a painful lingering death
i fear most in my in my life to drown, even though I am like a fish when it comes to water and love to swim
i fear being a failure in life in the sight of the people that I know. Failure can come from an inability to run one's life properly to not caring for one's body and getting a preventable disease
i fear not having enough money to survive when I stop working.  Note I do not say retirement - I suspect the company I slave for will terminate my employment long before I am ready to stop working
i know it sounds weird but the thing I fear most in life are fern spores. The seeds that grow on the bottom of fern leaves. I don't know what started the fear but they have always creeped me the heck out
i mostly fear missing opportunities and experiences in life. Life is far too short and I fear that I won't be able to make the best of it
i fear not being able to accomplish all my goals and experiencing all that life has to offer in this short life
losing everything
losing my family
what i can't see, what i don't know, and what is in the Dark
getting old!
failure
i fear losing the people I love (friends and family). I also fear never finding the right guy in my life
i fear lions
i fear losing my wife to an illness
i fear what comes after death. I also fear sharks
the one thing that I fear the most is heights. I have a genuine fear of anything that leaves the ground be it getting on a plane to just taking two steps up on a ladder
the one thing i fear the most in my life is losing my family members or loved ones
isolation and poverty
i am deathly afraid of heights!!!
i fear the future! The uncertainties of life and growing old. Will I have enough money to support myself in my golden years?
death by drowning
i guess it's getting older and looking like an old lady. Sad...
being alone
getting older and being unable to work anymore
failure
it would be snakes. I must have a phobia for snakes. I can't even see a small snake and not fear it. It's like my whole existence comes to an end when i see a snake.
losing my husband. That makes me very sad indeed. He is 64 years old and I am 49 years of age
public buses
what I fear the most in life is to get to the end and discover I spent so much of my time trying to earn a living that I didn't have any time to actually live it
the pain associated with dying
being alone
i fear that I may be a disappointment to my son
not being successful
for me, it is simple: non-existence. While I enjoy philosophy and theosophy, nothing has ever helped with the background fear of not being
drowning, especially at night in dark water
i fear being a failure. A failure as a wife, as a mother, as an employee. A failure amongst my friends. That is my fear
when I was 6 my father had a snake and tried to break me of this fear by forcing me to put it around my neck, however I think he made things worse
losing control (I have a mental illness)
i am afraid that I may have let too much time slip by without completing projects that were very important to me. So, I have decided to just get out there and do some painting and some other creative ventures and stop fretting over money
i fear that I will have to bury one of my children
disappointing those around me
i fear being alone as I get older in life. Not having someone in my life to love
i fear losing what I currently have and trying to make a place for myself somewhere else
if I lose what I have and where I am at I do not know what I would do
i fear dying suddenly while my children are still young and not being able to watch them grow up
losing family members
i fear most in this life that If I will not fulfill the commandments of God, he will be displeased with me
dying alone, without anyone to care about my being gone
the loss of a family member. I have experienced the loss of close members of my family recently, and I fear losing someone else close to me
i fear the unknown. I can deal and handle any situation presented with, but the unknown there is no way to be prepared
the thing I fear the most is being alone for the rest of my life once my son leaves home for Job Corps
what I fear the most is dying slowly by a disease such as having cancer or being  tormented by alzheimers
being alone
i fear the idea of failure and of my daughter seeing me as one
the one thing that I fear most is death. It's due to the fact that it's so final but also it's unknown. What really happens in the afterlife?
i fear tornadoes, snakes and spider mainly
dealing with the death of loved ones and feeling lonely, with no friends and no one to turn to for emotional support
dying in fear or pain
being insignificant
losing my independence in my personal life
i fear the death of my mother the most. She is getting up in years and she is all I have in this world
i fear trusting people who shouldn't be trusted
losing the ones I love. And Tornadoes. They are just about tied
i fear God the most in my life
my biggest fear is not being successful and not reaching my full potential
i fear living without my spouse and children
my kids getting hurt or dying
that the only thing that follows death is Nothingness
since I was young I have feared clowns. I still do to this day
failure
death of my loved ones
dying alone
my worst fear in my life is to outlive any of my children
i fear not being able to provide for my family. The thought of my children going hungry is completely unnerving to me
leaving this world alone
being alone forever
i fear that one day I might look back on my life and realize I did not accomplish my goals
flying in planes
snakes
what i fear most in life is being left alone with no family or friends
being left alone by everyone I hold dear
uncertainty, situations beyond my control
i fear losing my parents
having to move back home
spiders. They give me chills
not having enough money to get me through life and living under a bridge in misery, hunger, and poor health
i fear the loss of loved ones
the death of my loved ones, or being alone at the end of my life
my greatest fear is dying and leaving my 2 daughters without a mother
what I fear most in the world is failure
letting down those I care for
something that scares me the most is losing people that mean something to me. Losing someone that is important to me scares me because I love a lot of people, and I don't want to lose these people
the thing I fear most in life is the death of those I love. I experienced this recently when my husband died and now I fear the loss of my child, siblings, parents, and my friends
heights
the biggest thing I fear is sharks
i fear not being there for the people in my life who need me most. I fear not being able to help them when they need it
there are 2 things I fear the most in this world (Other than god): snakes and spiders!
failure
my husband dying (he's in army)
people not actually laughing at my jokes and antics but rather laughing at me. Not thinking I am funny at all
what I fear is dying and nothing being there
becoming a burden to my son
not having anyone to share my life with and dying alone
i am absolutely terrified of spiders. I cannot even look at an image of a spider without freaking out
not figuring out what to do/navigating my career path/feeling fulfilled by my work
going into debt and not being able to pay bills, loans etc. I don't need to be rich, just enough money to pay bills, have a home, and eat
i fear getting cancer and dying a horrible, painful, awful death. My Dad was diagnosed with cancer at a young age, and although he has beaten it several times in his life, I have a feeling I am going to get it at some point
not being able to support myself
i fear that many people who I love and know will spend eternity in hell. The fire of hell is real and I fear that my loved ones will end up there unless they come to Christ
pain
my biggest fear is never accomplishing my career goals
my health is good but I fear financial stress the most in my life
being alone when my husband is no longer with me
fear living on the street without a home, alone
i fear the embodiment of evil in our world
frogs, lizards, and butterflies
spiders
my worse fear is not achieving my goal of being a songwriter. I love to sing and I love to write songs but I fear rejection most of all
snakes
snakes
lots of things: being robbed, having my identity stolen, not being able to earn enough money to live
speaking in front of a group. It doesn't matter if I know the audience or not, it just terrifies me
being a failure
failure
i fear my parents falling ill
a painful or slow death
i fear being without a place to live/stay
the main thing I fear in life is being unsuccessful and not having a purpose
the biggest thing I fear most in life is being alone. I fear that one day everyone who I care about and love will leave me, either physically move away or pass away
the fear to let go. I feel that it's hard to move on and just let go of what you love. It's hard for me and sometimes brings me to tears
not living up to my potential
falling off a building or drowning in the ocean or getting eatten by a shark
i fear the Internal Revenue Service!
i fear that my children will fall under the pressure to afford the high life and won't actually work to enjoy life, but work to fill a bank account. I fear they'll look at how much their father and I work and will fall into the same rut
i fear that when my children look at me they'll remember a mother who was always working and never seemed to have time for a tea party. I fear my legacy
dying alone
not being able to support my family
i fear not being able to succeed in leading others to do the right thing
something happening to my wife or daughter
getting too old, too fast, and dying without having lived a fulfilling life. To see people in their last years having so many regrets
not making enough money to enjoy retirement, having to ask my future children for help
ifear not being able to take care of myself and having to rely on others when I've had plenty of time to make sure it doesn't happen. I fear being a burden
my partner dying
i fear Death
i am still fearful of public speaking, even at the tender age of 52
leaving this world before I feel like I have found my true purpose. I want no regrets when I go!
the thing I fear the most is an inability to make decisions for myself. I fear being left in a situation where I do not have a single choice, where I'm being forced to do something I don't want to do
growing so old that I am left to the mercy of the decisions of others. How will they know the decision is what I wanted?  Will They take advantage of me?
failure
the thing I fear most in life is losing my youth
losing my job
having to watch my loved ones pass from this life
i fear spiders.  They are big and have legs and run faster than me it seems
i fear not being able to take care of myself, as I get older
i fear failure the most in life. We are pressured to always be the best at everything in life and some of us are often unable to meet those requirements
i fear that I will fail in certain areas in life and let down those around me as well as myself
getting cancer
taking chances. Basically, the fear of failure I guess you could say
i fear not knowing what tomorrow brings
i am terrified of mice!
relying on my parents or someone else forever
i fear flying. I have flown a few times in my life, but i really am afraid of flying
that I will forever stand in the shadow of who I could have been
unrecognized potential and squandered opportunity loom large before me, their long penumbrae darkening my vision in the afternoon hours of my life. But mostly, day to day, I fear spiders
the thing I fear most in my life is that my daughter dies before me. I really wouldn't know how to deal with that
hepatitis C
what I fear the most in my life is having come to the end of my life and realizing that I never really lived
i truly have an odd fear of failure. Some people would equate this to social anxiety
cockroaches,rats and death!
what I fear the most in life, is being poor for the rest of my life. I do not want to struggle financially until I pass on in life. I believe I have a chance at success, if I keep motivated, determined, and never give up hope
failure.  That's definitely gotta be the biggest fear in my life.  I've always been a bit of a perfectionist
i believe all things are attainable - everything can be achieved. But, just the existence of that ugly word (failure) is enough to give me shivers
millipedes
i fear rejection in my personal life the most 
i go out of my way to avoid even giving tiny opinions to anyone that means anything to me
i fear losing my memories through something like dementia. What is the point of living if you have forgot your life?
snakes! They are slimy and disgusting
i fear that i will not succeed any further in life due to high unemployment rates and difficulty of getting ahead in life. Turking isn't making it easy to pay the bills
the things that I fear most in my life involve losing control. I also fear Panic and Anxiety
the dentist
i hate things like snakes, mice, roaches, almost any freaky looking bugs. But the thing that will really make me freak out is grasshoppers
buildings with slanted floors
i fear being alone, not having my significant other to be there day in and day out to hold me and love me for who I am
failure
i fear having to raise my sons alone, without a great male role model and having them follow in the footsteps of men who have only ever failed their children and families
loneliness
my baby getting hurt. I worry about me not paying attention well enough and something happening or someone hurting her
finding out that my life did not matter to anyone
running out of money
losing people that I love
what I fear the most in my life is losing my mother. She is very lovely and caring. She is the most important woman in my life and I am glad that she has always protected me from everything
i am afraid of crossing big bridges.  If they are really high they make me nauseous
being alone. I have done things that ther people would call crazy to avoid being homeless and alone. I've moved in with strangers I met on the internet on the opposite coast
my biggest fear is being alone because I feel that I need someone to love and be near me always. I do not like to feel void. I have to feel needed or wanted
dwarfs with hammers
aging
not being loved
a death of one of my children or spouse